YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 8. Community Associations
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IV. COMMUNITY ASSOCIATIONS FILES
  - Subseries B. 1988-2002
    - Wisconsin
      - Milwaukee, Greater
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994, 1996 (Box 962)
        - Correspondence, 1988-99 (Box 962)
        - Program, 1989-99, n.d. (Box 962)
      - Racine
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 962)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 962)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 962)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 962)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1975-98 (Box 962)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001 (Box 962)
        - Program, 1991, 1997, n.d. (Box 962)
      - Rock County/Janesville
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 962)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 962)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 962)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 962)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994, 1996 (Box 962)
        - Correspondence, 1987-99 (Box 962)
        - Program, 1990-97, n.d. (Box 962)
      - Stateline Area (Beloit)
        - General, 1985-95 (Box 962)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991 (Box 962)
      - Waukesha/Christoph Memorial
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 962)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 962)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 962)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 962)
        - Board of Directors, 1989-90, 1995-97 (Box 962)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1990-96 (Box 962)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001 (Box 962)
        - Pool Site Inspection report, 1991 (Box 962)
        - Program, 1988-98, n.d. (Box 963)
      - Wausau
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 963)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 963)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 963)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 963)
        - Board of Directors, 1994-99, n.d. (Box 963)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994, 1996 (Box 963)
        - Correspondence, 1991-99 (Box 963)
        - Program, 1990-98, n.d. (Box 963)
    - Wyoming
      - Sweetwater County (Rock Springs)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1989-99 (Box 963)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1990-99 (Box 963)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 964)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 964)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1977-99 (Box 964)
        - Correspondence, 1983-97 (Box 964)
        - Program, 1985-2000, n.d. (Box 964)